Inventory of the Fanxi Wang Correspondence, 1962-1987
Hoover Institution Archives
Fanxi Wang Correspondence,
1962-1987
88043
Wang, Fanxi, 1907-
1 folder 0.1 linear feet)
Hoover Institution Archives Stanford, California 94305-6010
Relates to activities of Trotskyist political groups in China and the United States, and analysis of political conditions in China and elsewhere. Consists primarily of letters received from the American Trotskyist C. Frank Glass
Administrative Information
Access
Collection is open for research
The Hoover Institution Archives only allows access to copies of audiovisual items. To listen to sound recordings or to view videos or films during your visit, please contact the Archives at least two working days before your arrival. We will then advise you of the accessibility of the material you wish to see or hear. Please note that not all audiovisual material is immediately accessible.
Acquisition Information
Acquired by the Hoover Institution Archives in 1988.
Accruals
Materials may have been added to the collection since this finding aid was prepared. To determine if this has occurred, find the collection in Stanford University's online catalog at http://searchworks.stanford.edu/. Materials have been added to the collection if the number of boxes listed in the online catalog is larger than the number of boxes listed in this finding aid.
Access Points
Fourth International; Communism--China; Communism--United States; Communism; China; United States--Politics and government; China--History--20th century; Socialist Workers Party
Inventory
- I. Original letters received from C. Frank Glass
  - 9/7 1966, 1
  - 11/18 1966, 2
  - 1/21 1967, 3
  - 11/3 1967, 4
  - 3/1 1968, 5
  - 4/3 1968, 6
  - 9/8 1968, 7
  - 11/30 1968, 8
  - 2/6 1969, 9
  - 6/6 1969, 10
  - 7/5 1969, 11
  - 8/13 1969, 12
  - 10/17 1969, 13
  - 12/6 1969, 14
  - 3/11 1970, 15
  - 3/31 1970, 16
  - 5/19 1970, 17
  - 6/26 1970, 18
  - 7/3 1970, 19
  - 7/27 1970, 20
  - 8/16 1970, 21
  - 9/20 1970, 22
  - 10/20 1970, 23
  - 11/17 1970, 24
  - 12/11 1970, 25
  - 2/5 1971, 26
  - 4/10 1971, 27
  - 6/24 1971, 28
  - 10/8 1971, 29
  - 10/13 1971, 30
  - 4/21 1972, 31
  - 7/6 1972, 32
  - 8/9 1972, 33
  - 11/7 1972, 34
  - 2/14 1973, 35
  - 4/11 1973, 36
  - 5/14 1973, 37
  - 5/28 1973, 38
  - 10/12 1973, 39
  - 11/19 1973, 40
  - 12/19 1973, 41
  - 3/30 1974, 42
  - 5/4 1974, 43
  - 10/29 1974, 44
  - 3/11 1975, 45
  - 7/23 1975, 46
  - 8/20 1975, 47
  - 3/27 1976, 48
  - 6/12 1976, 49
  - 6/25 1976, 50
  - 8/25 1976, 51
  - 11/24 1976, 52
  - 12/21 1976, 53
  - 2/9 1977, 54
  - 6/6 1977, 55
  - 9/19 1977, 56
  - 11/30 1977, 57
  - 2/23 1978, 58
  - 4/14 1978, 59
  - 8/19 1978, 60
  - 12/27 1978, 61
  - 1/19 1979, 62
  - 2/16 1979, 63
  - 5/1 1979, 64
  - 6/18 1979, 65
  - 7/14 1979, 66
  - 9/18 1979, 67
  - 10/17 1979, 68
  - 11/14 1979, 69
  - 12/5 1979, 70
  - 12/27 1979, 71
  - 2/16 1980, 72
  - 12/9 1980, 73
  - 1/23 1981, 74
  - 3/13 1981, 75
  - 9/21 1981, 76
  - 11/15 1982, 77
  - 5/19 1984, 78
  - 10/26 1984, 79
  - 10/14 1985, 80
  - 8/4 1987, 81
  - 8/24 1987, 82
- II. Miscellaneous
  - Partial text of letter, probably to Y.Y. Wang, signed by Farrell Dobbs, dated 1962., 1.
  - Letter to C. Frank Glass from Joseph Hansen dated 18 January 1967., 2.
  - Letter to Joseph Hansen by C. Frank Glass dated 10 April 1971., 3.
  - Letter to Gregor Benton by C. Frank Glass dated 24 December 1977., 4.
  - Letter to Joseph Hansen by C. Frank Glass dated 24 December 1977., 5.
  - Letter to Y.Y. Wang (?) from Natalia Bombaro, dated 29 March 1978., 6.
  - Letter to Y.Y. Wang from Joseph Hansen, dated 31 July 1978., 7.
  - Letter to Y.Y. Wang from Joseph Hansen dated 26 August 1978., 8.
  - Letter to Louis Sinclair from C. Frank Glass dated 24 July 1984., 9.
  - Letter to C. Frank Glass from Y.Y. Wang dated 22 October 1985., 10.